freemusicarchive.org 2019-04-27

# Privacy Policy | KitSplit

Last Updated: March 22, 2017 

Welcome! Your privacy is important to us. This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) describes how KitSplit Inc. (“we,” “our,” or “us”) collects, uses and shares personal information and other data (collectively, the “Information”) when operating the KitSplit online service and our website at www.kitsplit.com (the “Site” and together with the online service are collectively referred to as the “Services”). 

##  INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT 

When you use the Services, including when you sign up to create an account, subscribe to our newsletter, contact us or rent gear, we collect different types of Information from or about you. We obtain this Information when you use our services as a renter or owner of gear. To build safety and trust among the KitSplit community members, we require every user of the Services to confirm certain details and provide specific types of information (such as a valid ID) before being able to complete a rental. 

The table below lists the different types of Information that KitSplit (or our service providers) may obtain. The table also indicates for what purposes we use such Information. 

**Types of Information** |  **How We use That Information**  
---|---  
**Profile Information** |   
  
Contact information, including your:

  * first and last name 
  * profession 
  * cell or other phone number 
  * home and/or office address 
  * email address 
  * social media account information (such as when you use the Facebook Sign In feature) 

| 

  * To verify your identity in connection with the creation of your account and use of the Services
  * To provide you with the Services, including managing your account and rentals
  * To send you our newsletter
  * To communicate with you about the Services and respond to your questions or requests
  * To send you promotional or marketing materials and other communications
  * To contact you about, and administer your participation in, special events, programs, surveys, contests, sweepstakes, and other offers or promotions
  * To enable you to post on our blog and interact with KitSplit through social media
  * To generate and analyze statistics about your use of the Services, improve the Services and customize content and your experience with the Services

Profile picture and other images you upload  | 

  * To verify your identity in connection with the creation of your account and use of the Services
  * To provide you with the Services

Links to personal website or pages such as portfolio, reel, LinkedIn or Imdb, and any other information you include to describe yourself or your business in your profile  | 

  * To provide you with the Services
  * To communicate with you about the Services and respond to your questions or requests
  * To promote the Services and your profile to other members of the Services
  * To send you promotional or marketing materials and other communications
  * To contact you about, and administer your participation in, special events, programs or surveys 

Gear information such as gear you are renting or looking to rent, photos, pricing and approximate location of the gear  | 

  * To provide you with the Services
  * To communicate with you about the Services and respond to your questions or requests
  * To send you promotional or marketing materials and other communications
  * To contact you about, and administer your participation in, special events, programs, surveys

**Information Required to Process Rentals** |   
Identification information, including your: 

  * date of birth
  * driver’s license or other government-issued photo ID
  * taxpayer identification number
  * last four of your Social Security number (although in some cases, we may need to obtain your full Social Security number)

| 

  * To verify your identity in connection with the creation of your account and use of the Services
  * To provide you with the Services, including managing your account and rentals
  * To process and record payments for gear rentals, including for tax or income reporting purposes
  * To address and respond to any questions or issues related to rentals

Payment information, including your: 

  * name
  * contact information
  * payment card number, expiration date, authorization number or security code, and billing address
  * bank account number and routing number
  * IP address

| 

  * To provide you with the Services
  * To process and record payments for gear rentals, including for tax or income reporting purposes
  * To process payments for deposits for the value of the equipment in connection with rentals
**Please note that we use a third party, Stripe, to process payments made through the Site. Stripe obtains the relevant payment information directly from you. Stripe’s use of your personal information is governed by their privacy policy, which is available at https://stripe.com/us/privacy.** 
  
Certificate of insurance, including your: 

  * name
  * address
  * type and amount of coverage

| 

  * To provide you with the Services
  * To confirm your insurance coverage for gear rentals
  * To address and respond to any questions or issues related to your insurance coverage and potential claims in the event of an incident

**Other Information** |   
Gear pick up or delivery information, including: 

  * name
  * contact information
  * address

| 

  * To provide you with the Services, including to pick up or deliver gear rented through our Services

Transaction information, including: 

  * when and where a rental has occurred and users involved
  * payment or transfer amounts
  * payment method
  * IP address
  * Device type, model and operating system

| 

  * To generate and analyze statistics about your use of the Services, improve the Services and customize content and your experience with the Services

In addition, we may use Information obtained from you or about you to: 

  * detect, prevent and respond to fraud or theft, violations of law or of our Terms of Use and other policies, or other misuse of the Services,
  * comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, contractual obligations and our policies, and
  * support our business operations and perform accounting, auditing and other internal functions.

##  INFORMATION AUTOMATICALLY COLLECTED ABOUT YOUR VISIT 

We may automatically receive information when you visit our Site, including through cookies, web beacons and other technologies. A cookie is a small amount of data (often including a unique identifier), that is sent to your browser from a website’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive or your device. We may use cookies to administer the Services, understand Services (and Site) usage and improve our content and offerings. We may also use cookies to collect aggregate information about Site users. The information collected for these purposes (including your IP address and other information collected by automated means) may be disclosed to or collected directly by our third-party web analytics service providers, such as Google Analytics. To learn more about opting out of these activities, click here: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. If you don't want cookies, most web browsers include an option that allows you to not accept them. However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, you may not be able to log in successfully and/or some features of KitSplit may not function properly. We do not currently respond to web browser “do not track” signals on this Site. 

##  INTEREST-BASED ADVERTISING 

On our Site, we and third parties may collect information about your online activities to provide you with advertising about services or products tailored to your interests. You may see certain ads on other websites because we or such third parties participate in advertising networks. Ad networks track your online activities over time by collecting information through automated means, including through the use of cookies, web server logs and web beacons. The information ad networks may collect includes information about your visits to websites that participate in the relevant advertising networks, such as the pages or advertisements you view and the actions you take on the websites. This data collection takes place both on our Services and on third-party websites or apps that participate in the ad networks. This process allows us and third parties to deliver more tailored advertising. In addition, it helps us track the effectiveness of our marketing efforts. To learn how to opt out of this ad network interest-based advertising, click [here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). 

##  WITH WHOM WE MAY SHARE YOUR INFORMATION 

We may share the information listed under the “Profile Information” section in the table above with other users and members of the KitSplit community. We also may share your Profile Information with business partners, as needed or appropriate. We may publish information listed in the “Gear information” row of the table above on social media sites and other third party sites to promote your listings. 

We may share your Information: 

  * with service providers who work on our behalf, such as cloud storage providers, and other third party partners that provide features or functionalities which we integrate into our Services, such as payment processors, insurance provider, email/SMS communication or marketing service companies, and courier or delivery service providers
  * as necessary or appropriate, with members of fraud and theft prevention networks in which we participate
  * as necessary or appropriate, with our attorneys, accountants, auditors or other advisors
  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or other legal process, or to comply with government reporting obligations
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary (a) to protect our rights, the integrity of the Services, or your safety or the safety of others, or (b) to detect, prevent, or respond to theft or fraud, violations of law or our policies or Terms of Use, or other misuse of the Services, and
  * to the extent reasonably necessary to proceed with the negotiation or completion of a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets (including in the event of a reorganization, dissolution or liquidation).

In addition, we may share aggregated, de-identified data with third parties for any purposes. 

##  SOCIAL MEDIA FEATURES 

The Site includes social media functions, such as the Facebook Login or Sign In features, or Facebook, Instagram and Twitter widgets. These functions and widgets may collect information about which pages users visit on the Site and the IP address of the device you use to connect to the Internet. The widgets may also set a cookie to ensure the features are functioning properly. Your interactions with the social media functions and widgets located on the Site or provided in connection with the Services are governed by the privacy policies of the companies that provide these functions and widgets. If you use any of the social media functions or widgets on this Site, we strongly suggest that you review the privacy policies of the companies that provide those functions and widgets. 

##  LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES, APPS OR SERVICES 

Our Services may contain links to other websites, apps or other online services for your convenience or information. These websites, apps and services are operated by companies not affiliated with KitSplit. Linked websites, apps or services may have their own privacy policies or notices, which we strongly encourage you to review. We are not responsible for the content and data handling practices of any third party websites, apps or services. 

##  CHILDREN 

KitSplit is not intended for and may not be used by children under the age of eighteen (18). We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 18 and we do not target our Site to children under the age of 18. You cannot sign up for a user account if you are under 18. If you learn that a child under the age of 13 has created a user account with KitSplit or provided us with personal information, please contact us at contact@kitsplit.com. 

##  PROTECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION 

We maintain appropriate administrative, technical, and physical safeguards designed to safeguard the personal information collected in connection with the Services. However, no information system can be 100% secure, so we cannot guarantee the absolute security of your information. Moreover, we are not responsible for the security of information you transmit to the Site over networks that we do not control, including the Internet and wireless networks. 

##  INTERNATIONAL USERS AND VISITORS 

KitSplit is hosted in the United States. Because the Internet is global, you should note that by providing your Information as an international visitor or user, you are: (i) permitting the transfer of your Information to the United States which may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you reside; and (ii) permitting the use, storage, sharing and other processing of Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

##  CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY 

We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice to you. Any changes to the Privacy Policy will be reflected on this page and will become effective immediately upon posting. If we make significant changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting a prominent notice on this Site. We also may notify you by email of such significant changes. Please check the effective date below to determine if there have been any changes since you have last reviewed the Privacy Policy. 

##  CONTACT US 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our use of your Information collected through the Site, please contact us at contact@kitsplit.com
